System Dynamic Society; Records ua435
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Conferences, 1976-2018
  - Cambridge, MA, USA, 1996
    - Proceedings, 1996
      - Genta, Peter J. with Neville Sokol, "A Microworld of Exploration and Development: Creating a Learning Laboratory for the Oil & Gas Industry", 1996
      - Georgantzas, Nicholas C. with Stephen H. Brovarone, "Globalizing High Sulfur Fuel Oil Marketing", 1996
      - Georgantzas, Nicholas C., "Reengineering Business Process Reengineering with System Dynamics", 1996
      - Gricic, Branko with Ante Munitic, "System Dynamics Approach to Validation", 1996
      - Groessler, Andreas, "Providing Simulation Models on the Internet", 1996
      - Grossman, M., "Designing Strategies to Achieve Sustainable Growth for Biotechnology Companies", 1996
      - Guerra, Juan Hernandez, "Studies of a Model of Entertainment Between Economic Cycles", 1996
      - Guthrie, Scott with Diana Fisher, "Systems Thinking and Systems Dynamics in the CC-STADUS High School Project", 1996
      - Hall, Roger with M.P. Gupta, "Using a Corporate System Model of a Firm to Investigate the Feedback Dynamics Leading to Growth, Decline, and Bankruptcy", 1996
      - Haslett, Tim with Charles Osborne, "Local Decision Rules: Complexity or Chaos?", 1996
      - Haslett, Tim, "Three Simulation for Teaching Systems Thinking", 1996
      - Hermann, John F. with John L. DeOlden, "A Flight Simulator for University Department Planning", 1996
      - Higuchi, Tohru, "Parameter Estimation Involved to System Dynamics Model by Multi-Objective Optimization Technique", 1996
      - Hines, James, "Modeling the Evolution of Organizations", 1996
      - Hines, James H. with Dewey Johnson, "Competitive Dynamics: Context, Model, Outcome, and Ongoing Use", 1996
      - Homer, Jack with Fred Nichols, "Enterprise Modeling at ETS: Highways and Biways", 1996
      - Hsiao, Naiyi, "Evaluating the Policy of Stratospheric Ozone Protection- a System Dynamic Modeling Approach", 1996
      - Huz, Steven with David F. Andersen, George P. Richardson and Roger Boothroyd, "Evaluating Group Model Building in Mental Health Vocational Services", 1996
      - Jambekar, Anil B., "A System View of Design Engineering Capacity: Continuous Improvement Policy Interaction", 1996
      - Jonas, Wolfgang, "Systems Thinking in Industrial Design", 1996
      - Jones, Andrew with Elizabeth Krahmer, Rogelio Oliva, Nelson Repenning, Scott Rockart and John Sterman, "Comparing Improvement Programs for Product Development and Manufacturing: Results from Field Studies", 1996
      - Jordao, Luis with M.P. Antunes and R.F. Santos, "Reactive vs. Proactive Corporate Environment Management: A System Dynamics Learning Environment", 1996
      - Joy, Timothy, "Crime and Astonishment", 1996
      - Kallenberg, Robert with Charles H. Fine, "Analysis and Business Cycles in the U.S. Machine Tool Industry", 1996
      - Kampmann, Christian E., "Feedback Loop Gains and System Behavior", 1996
      - Karsky, Michel with Stephane Copin and Sonia Pitrach, "The Implementation of a Large System Dynamics Model of Human Behavior", 1996
      - Khalil, Yahia F. with Michael Radzicki, "The Dynamics of the Zero-Emission Vehicle Industry", 1996
      - Kim, Doa Hoon with Dong-Hwan Kim, "How Heuristic are Heuristic Decision Rules in a Dynamic Game?", 1996
      - Kim, Dong- Hwan with Jae-Ho Juhn, "Dynamics of Networks: System Dynamics Model for Network Externality and Critical Mass", 1996
      - Koenig, Ulli H., "Use of Simulation in Management and Management Education: Speeding up the Wheel of Learning?", 1996
      - Koerstein, Ralf with Bernd Viehweger, "Evaluation of Neutral Networks via Generic Modelling using System Dynamics", 1996
      - Krahmer, Elizabeth M. with Scott Rockart, "Carbon Sequestration and Emission Management: A Costal Rican Case Study", 1996
      - Kunsberg, Phillip, "An Interactive Simulation of a Manufacturing Enterprise: Prelimimary Observations", 1996
      - Lane, David, "Can We Have Confidence in Generic Structures?", 1996
      - Langley, Paul with John Morecroft, "Learning from Microworlds Environments: A Summary of the Research Issues", 1996
      - Lao, Hong Mou, "Energy Capacity Management for the Industrial Sector of Zhejiang Province in China: A System Dynamics Model", 1996
      - Larsen, Erik R. with Alessandro Lomi, "The Dynamics of Organizational Inertia, Survival and Change", 1996
      - Lehmann, Frank, "A System View of the Design of Modern Manufacturing Systems", 1996
      - Lopez Paredes, Adolfo with Alfonso Redondo Castan and Ricardo del Olmo Martinez, "The Spanish Glass Container Maker. A Model of Strategic Planning in a Firm", 1996
      - Lyneis, James M. with Alexander L. Pugh III, "Automated vs. 'Hand' Calibration of System Dynamics Models: An Experiment With a Simple Project Model", 1996
      - MacDonald, Roderick H., "Discrete Versus Continuous Formulation: A Case Study Using Coyle's Aircraft Carrier Survivability Model", 1996
      - Macedo, Julio with Rafael Ruiz Usano, "An Intelligent System Dynamics Based controller for Fuzzy Managerial System", 1996
      - Machuca, Jose A. D. with Miguel A. Domingo Carrillo, "Transparent- Box Business Simulator verus Black- Box Business Simulators: an Initial Empirical Comparative Study", 1996
      - Madachy, Raymond, "Modeling Software Processes with System Dynamics: Current Developments", 1996
      - Madwed, Albert, "Systems Thinking for K-12 Teachers: A New Course at the Graduate School of Education and Allied Professions, Fairfield University", 1996
      - Maier, Frank with Juergen Strohhecker, "Do Management Flight Simualtors Really Enhance Decision Effectiveness?", 1996
      - Maier, Frank, "Substitution Among Successive Product Generations- An Almost Neglected Problem In Innovation Diffusion Models", 1996
      - Maliapen, Mahendran with Ram Ramasehan and M. Quaddus, "System Dynamics Approach to Marketing Modeling in the Airline Industry", 1996
      - Mandal, Purnendu with Amrik S. Sohal, "Modeling Quality Improvement Processes", 1996
      - Mandal, Purnendu with Amrik S. Sohal, "Understanding Long Term Interactions in Fabricated Metal Manufacturing Industry: A Case", 1996
      - Mashayekhi, Ali N., "Oscillation in Preventitive Maintenance Programs", 1996
      - Mayberry, Matt with Kent Hoxsey, Kerry McCracken and Carl Rendell, "Using Systems Thinking and Dynamics Simulations to Reengineer Manufacturing Processes at Silicon Graphics", 1996
      - Milling, Peter, "A Management Stimulator to Support Group Decision Making in a Corporate Gaming Environment", 1996
      - Moizer, Jonathan D., "Safely Knowledge and its Influence over Accidents in the Workplace", 1996
      - Mojtahedzadeh, Mohammad with David F. Andersen, "Assessing the System-wide Impacts of Automated Voice Response Customer Service Technologies", 1996
      - Mollona, Eduardo, "The Dynamics of Organizational Heuristics and Biases in Corporate Strategy", 1996
      - Moon, Tae Hoon with Deuk Jong Bae, Doa Hoon Kim and Dong Whan Kim, "Comparing Strategies for Building Korean Information Infrastructure Using a System Dynamic Model", 1996
      - Morecoft, John, "A Behavioral Model of Diversification and Performance in a Mature Industry", 1996
      - Morita, Michiya with Nobuhide Tanaka, Yutaka Takahashi and Toru Higuchi, "Linkage Structure and Trade-offs of Competitive Measures", 1996
      - Moxnes, Erling, "Crisis Management of a Renewable Resource", 1996
      - Moxnes, Erling, "Stochastic Optimization in Policy Space Using Simulation Models", 1996
      - Oliva, Rogelio, "Empirical Validation of a Dynamic Hypothesis", 1996
      - Parayno, Phares P., "Poverty-Environment Links in the Philippines", 1996
      - Park, Hun-Joon with Jimwoo Kim, Kuen S. Yi and Kiho Jun, "Enhancing the Performance in Dynamic Decision Making: The Adaptive Model Reconstruction Using Feedforward vs. Feedback Decision Strategy", 1996
      - Piatelli, Mauro with Nicola Bianchi and Luca Minna, "Note on Conceptual Distance in Simulation using the Polls Model as a Basis for Discussion", 1996
      - Qu, Weishhuang with Gerald O. Barney and Jos Verbeek, "RMSM-X in Vensim: Refining the Financial Sector of the Threshold 21 National Development Model", 1996
      - Reichelt, Kimberly S. with James M. Lyneis and Carl G. Bespolka, "Calibration Statistics: Selecting a Statistic and Settling a Standard", 1996
      - Repenning, Nelson, "Modeling the Failure of Productivity Improvement Programs", 1996
      - Rios, Jose Perez with Markus Schwaninger, "Integrative Systems Modeling: Leveraging Complementarities of Qualitative and Quantitative Methodologies", 1996
      - Roberts, James C., "The Stucture of Structural Violence", 1996
      - Rodrigues, Alexandre J.G. with Terry Williams, "System Dynamics in Project Management: Assesing the Impacts of Client Behavior in Project Management", 1996
      - Rodrigues, Alexandre J.G. with Terry Williams, "System Dynamics in Software Project Management: Towards the Development of a Formal Integrated Framework", 1996
      - Roos, Egbert, "System Dynamics Modeling: A Case Study from the Software Product Development", 1996
      - Root, Gus with Grant McGriffin, "They will Learn what They See Others Doing", 1996
      - Rothman, Johanna, "Applying Systems Thinking to the Issues of Software Product Development", 1996
      - Rouwette, Etienne with Jac Vennix, "The Influence of Group Model Building on Policy Intentions", 1996
      - Ruiz Usano, Rafael with Jose Manuel Framinan Torres, Adolfo Crespo Marquez and Ricardo Zubiria de Castro, "System Dynamics and Discrete Stimulation in a Constant Work-in-Process System: A Comparative Study", 1996
      - Ruth, Matthias, "Exploring Spatio- Temporal Dynamics in Economic Exchange: A Dynamic Modeling Approach", 1996
      - Ryan, Thomas, "A Peircian Framework for Using System Dynamics Modeling as an Inquiry System", 1996
      - Sahara, Kanji with Kinya Machida, Nobuyuki Suzuki and A. Uchino, "Environmental Model of Atmosphere- from Japan Model to East Asian Companies", 1996
      - Santoni, Marco, "A Stimulation Model Behaviour of Innovative Companies", 1996
      - Sedhi, Habib with Carmine Bianchi, "A Winery Dynamic Model for "Product Portfolio" Management", 1996
      - Sedhi, Habib, "SYDIC- System Dynamics- Italian Chapter", 1996
      - Shafto, Syvia A. with CJ Kalin and Michael G. Shafto, "Cognitive and Instructional Issues in System Modeling", 1996
      - Shawwash, Ziad K. with S.O. Dennis Russell, "Use of System Dynamics for Managing Water in Jordan", 1996
      - Sitompul, Rislima F. with Muhammad Tasrif, "A System Dynamics View of the Rural Community Development in Indonesia", 1996
      - Smith, Andrew with Allen Boorstein, "A Systemic Approach to System Dynamics Education: A Status Report", 1996
      - Smith, Ricardo with Santiago Montoya, Carlos Jamie Franco and Issac Dyner, "Assessing the Dynamics of Energy Markets Under Liberalisation Process", 1996
      - Smits, Cyprian A. with E.J. Verroen, "A System Dynamics Model for Long Term Travel Demand Forecasting and Policy Analysis", 1996
      - Sotaquira, G. Ricardo with Hugo Andrade and Lilia Nayibe Gelvez, "Organizational Design with System Dynamics and Radical Change Approach", 1996
      - Sridharan, Sanjeev, "Can Vector- Autoregression Methodology Help in an Understanding of the Casual Dynamics of the Unemployment- Crime Relationships?", 1996
      - Stave, Krystyna A., "Redefining Resources: A Systems Perspective on the Watershed Protection Conflict Between New York City and the Catskill Mountain Region", 1996
      - Stefano, Julia M Di, "Edutaining, Engaging the Learner, and System Dynamics", 1996
      - Sterman, John D. with Nelson Repenning, Rogelio Oliva, Elizabeth Krahmer, Scott Rockart and Andrew Jones, "The Improvement Paradox: Designing Sustainable Quality Improvement Programs", 1996
      - Sterman, John D. with Rebecca Henderson, Eric Beinhocker and Lee I. Newman, "A Behavioural Analysis of Learning Curve Strategy", 1996
      - Sturges, Stephen with Graham Winch, "Computer Attack: The Role of Modeling in Development an Intergrated Securtiy Policy", 1996
      - Sturtevant, Rochelle, "The Effect of Nutrient Recycling on Ecosystem Stability", 1996
      - Suksawang, Orasa, "System Dynamics Approach to Managing Community Development", 1996
      - Sunaryo, Prasetyo with Tusy A. Adbroto, Hary Budiarto and Ervan Maksum, "Application of Sysytem Dynamics on Watershead Management on Java Island, Indonesia", 1996
      - Sycamore, Douglas, "Improving Software Project Management Through System Dynamics Modeling", 1996
      - Tasrif, Muhammad, "The Implications of Environmental Consideration in Energy Development to the General Economic Welfare and Development in Indonesia", 1996
      - Thiel, Daniel, "Instabilities and Deterministic Chaos In Just-In-Time Production Systems: Comparison between Neutral Networks Stimulation and Continuous Stimulation", 1996
      - Tosteson, Joshua, "Systems Dynamics and Earth Systems Science: Bridging the Gaps Between Research and Education", 1996
      - Trees, W. Scott with James K. Doyle and Micheal J. Radizcki, "Using Cognitive Styles Typology to Explain Dynamics Decision Making in a Computer Stimulated Environment", 1996
      - Wang, Qifan, "A Systems Dynamics Study of the Coordinated Development of Regional Infastructure", 1996
      - Wang, Wanlong with Jerry Fuh and X Yongnian, "Dynamic Analysis of Manufacturing Systems", 1996
      - Wile, Kristina with David Smilonich, "Using Dynamic Stimulation for Resource Management Policy Design at the Minnesota Department of Transportation", 1996
      - Willey, Phillip C.T. with Amil K. Bajpai, "A Systems Dynamic Model of Manufacturing Quality Costs and Benefits", 1996
      - Wolstenholme, Eric, "Community Care for the Elderly in the UK", 1996
      - Wyatt, Ray, "Strategic Planning Using Neutral Network-based, Delphi, Workshop Software", 1996
      - Xiang, Gang with Liu Linhong, "A System Dynamics Model for an Enterprise's Sustainable Innovation Process", 1996
      - Xu, Qingruil with Jie Han, Bin Guo and Jin Chen, "Hi-Tech Impulse: A New Coordinative Development Pattern of Social- Economy- Technology-Education Systems", 1996
      - Yang, Jenshou, "Facilitating Learning Through Goal Setting in a Learning Laboratory", 1996
      - Young, Showing H. with Chai Ping Chen, "Entrapping Landmine Structure in Microworlds Formed with Uncontrollable Positive Feedback Loops", 1996
      - Young, Showing H. with Shih-Hui Lo, "Experiences in Designing Board-type Stimulation Games for Center Satellite Industrial System", 1996
      - Young, Showing H. with Sy-Feng Wang, "Measuring the Learning of Systems Thinking: Theory and Method", 1996
      - Yu, Jia-Di with Xin-Yun Zeng, "Study on Development Strategies of Regional Water Resources System", 1996
      - Yu, Lijuan, "Guided by Learning Organization to Practice a Process Reengineering for an Enterprise Business", 1996
      - Zagonel, Aldo, "A Dynamics Model for Analyzing Urban Growth in a Planned City", 1996
      - Zamudio-Ramirez, Pavel with Andrew Spicer, John Sterman, Steve Eppinger and John Ehrenfeld, "Economics of Automobile Recycling", 1996
      - Zaraza, Ronald with Diana Fisher, "Experiences in Developing Single-Discipline and Cross- Curricular Models for Classroom Use", 1996
  - Tokyo, Japan, 1995
    - Conference Website, 1995
    - Abstracts, 1995
    - Volume I: Plenary Programs, 1995
      - Acharya, Surya Raj with Khalid Saeed, "A Search for an Operational Environmental Policy Based on the "Limits to Growth" Study", 1995
      - Barney, Gerald O. with Robert Eberlein, Weishuang Qu and P.D. Sharma, "The Threshold 21: Sustainable Development Model", 1995
      - Choucri, Nazli with Rebecca Berry, "Sustainability and lateral Issues: A Model", 1995
      - Fiddaman, Thomas, "Formulation Experiments with a Simple Climate/ Economy Model", 1995
      - Ford, Andrew, "System Dynamics and the Sustainable Development of the Electric Power Industry", 1995
      - Ginsberg, Ari with John Morecroft, "Systems Thinking and the Case Method", 1995
      - Higa, Teruo, "Soft Landing into the Twenty- First Century: The Requirements", 1995
      - Kim, Dong-Hwan with Jae-Ho Jun, "Hierarchical Approach in System Dynamics Modeling", 1995
      - Kodama, Fumio, "Techno-Paradigm Shift and its Research Methodology", 1995
      - Lane, David, "The Folding Star: A Comparative Reframing and the Extension of Validity Concepts in System Dynamics", 1995
      - Milling, Peter M., "Managing and Understanding Technological Innovations", 1995
      - Morita, Michiya with Nobuhide Tanaka, Harunori Mori and Yutaka Takahashi, "Communication Network Systems for Competitiveness: The Japanese World Class Manufacturing Case", 1995
      - Myrtveit, Magne, "Models Crossing the Boundaries of Tools", 1995
      - Piattelli, M. with R.G. Coyle, "On The Modeling of Sea Power: An Extension of the Polis Model in a Competitive Scenario", 1995
      - Radzicki, Michael J. with W. Scott Trees, "A System Dynamics Approach to Sustainable Cities", 1995
      - Richardson, George P., "Chaos from Generic Structures: A Cautionary Tale", 1995
      - Richardson, George P., "Problems for the Future of System Dynamics", 1995
      - Saeed, Khalid, "The Organization of Learning in System Dynamics Practice", 1995
      - Sterman, John with Nelson Repenning and Fred Kofman, "Unanticipated Side Effects of Successful Quality Programs: Exploring a Paradox of Organizational Improvement", 1995
      - Winch, Graham W., "Understanding the Dynamics of Technology Switching in Seeking to Maintain International Competitiveness", 1995
      - Wolstenholme, Eric F., "Systems Thinking, System Dynamics", 1995
      - Zahn, Erich with Jurgen Greschner, "Strategic Evalution of Flexible Assembly Systems-Combining Hard and Soft Decision Criteria", 1995
    - Volume II: Parallel Programs, 1995
      - Akkermans, Henk, "Quantifying the Soft Issues: A Case Study in the Banking Industry", 1995
      - Aoki, Toshiaki with Hajime Inamura, "An Urban Growth Modeling Based On Urban Attraction", 1995
      - Aslam, Javaid with Khalid Saeed, "Electricity Conservation in Domestic Sector of Pakistan: A System Dynamics Approach", 1995
      - Bajpai, Anil K. with Phillip C.T. Wiley, "Dynamic Model of Purchasing Quality", 1995
      - Banerjee, Souvik with Mohit Junja and Pratap K. J. Mohapatra, "IGRASP-A System Dynamics Software Package With Automatic Code Generation Facility", 1995
      - Bianchi, Carmine, "An Educational Dynamic Model for Net Working Capital Management in a Trading Wholesale Firm", 1995
      - Bianchi, Carmine with Habib Sedehi, "Dynamic Modeling for "Products Portfolio" Management and New Products Launching", 1995
      - Brooke, Kathleen, "The Momentum Of Success: The Role of Construction in the Thailand Economic Boom", 1995
      - Cavaleri, Steven with John Sterman, "Towards Evaluation of Systems Thinking Interventions: A Case Study", 1995
      - Cavana, R.Y. with R.D. Hughes, "Strategic Modeling for Competitive Advantage", 1995
      - Chen, Jin with Xu Qingrui and Shao Shaomin, "A System Thinking Approach to Select Avenue of Science & Technology Development", 1995
      - Clark, Thomas D. with Hironori Kurono, "A Conversion Table of DYNAMO into STELLA II", 1995
      - Das, Bhakta with Manas Bandyopadhyay and Pratap K. J. Mohapatra, "System Dynamics Modeling of an Activated Sludge Plant", 1995
      - Di Stefano, Julia, "From Control to Chaos: A System Dynamics model of Interpersonal Communication", 1995
      - Dowling, Anne M. with Roderick H. MacDonald and George P. Richardson, "Simulation of Systems Archetypes", 1995
      - Egol, Morton, "Information Age Accounting: Catalyst and Enable of the Self-Organizing Enterprise", 1995
      - Forest, Tom, "Sustainable Civilization: Cohesion, Capacity and External Contacts", 1995
      - Ganter, Susan L. with James K. Doyle and Micheal J. Radzicki, "Assessing System Dynamics Curricula: Past, Present and Future", 1995
      - Genta, Peter J. with Donald A. Seville, "Economic Lift-Off, Boom and Bust: A System Dynamics View of the Bangkok, Thailand Economy 1980-1992", 1995
      - Georgantzas, Nicolas C. with James S. Fraser and Elvan Tugsuz, "Bipartisan Process Improvement in Polymer Coating: Combining System Dynamics with Statistical Process Control (SPC)", 1995
      - Georgantzas, Nicolas C. with Sharon P. Smith and James S. Fraser, "Allocation Dynamics of Resources Imperiled: AACSB, Students and Professors", 1995
      - Georgantzas, Nicolas C. with Andreas Schulte, "Can Consummate Concentric, Conglomerate, Constrained And Contractual Creatures Create Value? An Intricate Shakespearean Impromptu on Romancing the Deal", 1995
      - Gill, Roderic, "An Integrated Social Fabric Matrix /System Dynamics Approach to Policy Analysis", 1995
      - Gill, Roderic, "Planning Sustainable Agro-Ecosystems: A System Dynamics Approach", 1995
      - Grobman, Martin U., "The Dynamics of Research and Development in the Pharmaceutical Industry--Productivity of Traditional versus New Research Technologies", 1995
      - Han, Jiuqiang with Guoji Sun, "System Dynamics Simulation Software--Dynamox", 1995
      - Heinbokel, John F. with P. Jeffery Potash, Martin Engelken and Robert Green, "Programs To Support the Development of System Dynamics-Based Curricula", 1995
      - Jia, Ren'an, "A Mathematical Definition System of System Dynamics", 1995
      - Kim, Dong-Hwan with Doa Kim, "System Dynamics Model for A Mixed Strategy Game Between Police and Driver", 1995
      - Kim, Dong-Hwan, "A New Approach for Finding Dominant Feedback Loops: Loop By Loop Simulation for Tracking Feedback Loop Gains", 1995
      - Mitsuo, Kishi with Hosoda Ryusuke, Yamada Tomoki and Funahashi Hiroki, "Transport Forecasting Based on Artificial Life Concept", 1995
      - Kojima, Takahiro with Yutaka Takahashi, Kinya Machida and Teiichi Igarashi, "System Dynamics Model of the Tokyo System", 1995
      - Lane, David, "Diary of an Oil Market Model: How an Interactive System Dynamics Modeling Process Was Used with Shell Managers t o Resolve Conflict and Generate Insight", 1995
      - Langley, Paul A., "Building Cognitive Feedback into a Microworld Learning Environment: Results from a Pilot Experiment", 1995
      - Lux, Nan with Eric Choi, "System Dynamics and The Internet", 1995
      - Maier, Frank H., "Understanding the Dynamics Created by Management Decisions- A Vensim-based Simulation Approach for Management Education", 1995
      - Maier, Frank H., "Innovation Diffusion Models for Decision Support in Strategic Management", 1995
      - Mandal, Purnendu, "Missing Links in Quality Initiatives in Australian Manufacturing Industry-A System Dynamics Analysis", 1995
      - Marquez, Adolfo with Rafael Usano and Antonio Herguedas, "Maintenance Models and System Dynamics", 1995
      - Melero, Rosa with Jose A.D. Machuca, "A Model for Learning about the Agricultural Business System", 1995
      - Mohapatra, Pratap K.L., "Use of System Dynamics Diagrammatic Tools as Representation Schemes for Linear Programming Models", 1995
      - Mohapatra, Pratap K.L., "Development and Maintenance Dynamics of a Software Business Firm", 1995
      - Mojtahedzadeh, Mohammad T. with George P. Richardson, "Confusion in the Polarity of Major Loops", 1995
      - Morgan, Tom with Bill Ammentorp, "Human Service Systems: A Theoretical Perspective", 1995
      - Musaphir, Hamza with Ostap Hawaleshka, "Understanding Strategy of a Manufacturing Based Learning Organization in Transition in the Twenty-First Century", 1995
      - Myrtveit, Magne, "Feeding Your Models with Real Business Data", 1995
      - Ogunlana, Stephen with Jason Lim and Khalid Saeed, "Civil Engineering Design Management Using a Dynamic Model", 1995